<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <description>Christian empowerment</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 22:03:11 +0300</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 22:03:11 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.8.5</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Test Article</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Christian organization that exists to educate, train and equip individuals to discover the gifts and talents that are locked up on the inside of them while developing a more intimate relationship with Christ Jesus. We offer mentor ship courses, conferences, speaking engagements, weddings and baptisms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our purpose is to help individuals discover their God given gifts and talents that are locked up on the inside of them to be developed through Mentor-ship, teaching and preaching.To encourage individuals to be intimate with God while developing a healthy balanced life . Win souls for the body of Christ using the demonstration of Gods Power. See the hungry fed, the sick healed, and souls in bondage set free&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/03/07/test-article.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/03/07/test-article.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The first mass-produced book</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;From a rectilinear format, at least in the United States, is thought to be this 1863 edition of Red Riding Hood, cut into the shape of the protagonist herself with the troublesome wolf curled at her feet. Produced by the Boston-based publisher Louis Prang, this is the first in their “Doll Series”, a set of five “die-cut” books, known also as shape books — the other titles being Robinson Crusoe, Goody Two-Shoes (also written by Red Riding Hood author Lydia Very), Cinderella, and King Winter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An 1868 Prang catalogue would later claim that such “books in the shape of a regular paper Doll… originated with us”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;It would seem the claim could also extend to die cut books in general, as we can’t find anything sooner, but do let us know in the comments if you have further light to shed on this! Such books are, of course, still popular in children’s publishing today, though the die cutting is not now limited to mere outlines, as evidenced in a beautiful 2014 version of the same Little Red Riding Hood story.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The die cut has also been employed in the non-juvenile sphere as well, a recent example being Jonathan Safran Foer’s ambitious Tree of Codes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for this particular rendition of Charles Perrault’s classic tale, the text and design is by Lydia Very (1823-1901), sister of Transcendentalist poet Jones Very. The gruesome ending of the original — which sees Little Red Riding Hood being gobbled up as well as her grandmother — is avoided here, the gore giving way to the less bloody aims of the morality tale, and the lesson that one should not disobey one’s mother.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/03/06/the-first-mass-produced-book.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/03/06/the-first-mass-produced-book.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>We all wait for summer</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This is changed. As I engage in the so-called “bull sessions” around and about the school, I too often find that most college men have a misconception of the purpose of education. Most of the “brethren” think that &lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;education should equip&lt;/a&gt; them with the proper instruments of exploitation so that they can forever trample over the masses. Still others think that education should furnish them with noble ends rather than means to an end.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It seems to me that education has a two-fold function to perform in the life of man and in society: the one is utility and the other is culture. Education must enable a man to become more efficient, to achieve with increasing facility the ligitimate goals of his life.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2018/01/12/we-all-wait-for-summer.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2018/01/12/we-all-wait-for-summer.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tree of Codes</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The first mass-produced book to deviate from a rectilinear format, at least in the United States, is thought to be this 1863 edition of Red Riding Hood, cut into the shape of the protagonist herself with the troublesome wolf curled at her feet. Produced by the Boston-based publisher Louis Prang, this is the first in their “Doll Series”, a set of five “die-cut” books, known also as shape books — the other titles being Robinson Crusoe, Goody Two-Shoes (also written by Red Riding Hood author Lydia Very), Cinderella, and King Winter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for this particular rendition of Charles Perrault’s classic tale, the text and design is by Lydia Very (1823-1901), sister of Transcendentalist poet Jones Very. The gruesome ending of the original — which sees Little Red Riding Hood being gobbled up as well as her grandmother — is avoided here, the gore giving way to the less bloody aims of the morality tale, and the lesson that one should not disobey one’s mother.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;It would seem the claim could also extend to die cut books in general, as we can’t find anything sooner, but do let us know in the comments if you have further light to shed on this! Such books are, of course, still popular in children’s publishing today, though the die cutting is not now limited to mere outlines, as evidenced in a beautiful 2014 version of the same Little Red Riding Hood story.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An 1868 Prang catalogue would later claim that such “books in the shape of a regular paper Doll… originated with us”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The die cut has also been employed in the non-juvenile sphere as well, a recent example being Jonathan Safran Foer’s ambitious Tree of Codes.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2018/01/12/tree-of-codes.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2018/01/12/tree-of-codes.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Red Riding Hood</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The first mass-produced book to deviate from a rectilinear format, at least in the United States, is thought to be this 1863 edition of Red Riding Hood, cut into the shape of the protagonist herself with the troublesome wolf curled at her feet. Produced by the Boston-based publisher Louis Prang, this is the first in their “Doll Series”, a set of five “die-cut” books, known also as shape books — the other titles being Robinson Crusoe, Goody Two-Shoes (also written by Red Riding Hood author Lydia Very), Cinderella, and King Winter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An 1868 Prang catalogue would later claim that such “books in the shape of a regular paper Doll… originated with us”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;It would seem the claim could also extend to die cut books in general, as we can’t find anything sooner, but do let us know in the comments if you have further light to shed on this! Such books are, of course, still popular in children’s publishing today, though the die cutting is not now limited to mere outlines, as evidenced in a beautiful 2014 version of the same Little Red Riding Hood story.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The die cut has also been employed in the non-juvenile sphere as well, a recent example being Jonathan Safran Foer’s ambitious Tree of Codes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for this particular rendition of Charles Perrault’s classic tale, the text and design is by Lydia Very (1823-1901), sister of Transcendentalist poet Jones Very. The gruesome ending of the original — which sees Little Red Riding Hood being gobbled up as well as her grandmother — is avoided here, the gore giving way to the less bloody aims of the morality tale, and the lesson that one should not disobey one’s mother.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/tutorial/2018/01/12/red-riding.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/jekyll/tutorial/2018/01/12/red-riding.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Jekyll</category>
        
        <category>tutorial</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
